(Sheldon:)Why would you do that?
(Amy:)This was a potential issue,
(Amy:)so I got out ahead of it
(Amy:)and I managed
the situation for you.
You "managed the situation."
(Amy:)That's right.
(Sheldon:)So my mother thought I was
incapable of finding a mate,
(Sheldon:)and my mate thinks I'm incapable
of running my own life.
Not your whole life!
(Amy:)I mean, science.
You got that.
(Amy:)Organizing your sock drawer,
you're the king.
(Amy:)But understanding
how other people are feeling,
(Amy:)that's a weak spot for you.
(Sheldon:)I have gotten
much better at that.
(Amy:)Have you?
How am I feeling right now?
What the... How should I know?
(Sheldon:)Excited? Itchy?
Give me the first letter.
(Amy:)You and I are in
a relationship.
(Amy:)I help you with
your shortcomings,
(Amy:)and you help me with mine.
(Sheldon:)How would you feel
if I contacted
(Sheldon:)your mother behind your back?
(Amy:)Delighted that you showed any
interest in my family at all?
"Delighted"?
(Sheldon:)What... Not if I guessed
for a hundred years.